&gt；&gt；steve kinney：好的，很酷，让我们来看看，我们发现了什么？
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: All right, cool, so
let's take a look, what do we find?
我们有没有从运行一些测试中得到任何初步的注意？
Do we have any first noticings
from running some of the tests?
&gt；&gt；steve kinney：我们注意到的任何事情，我们都可以一起做。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Anything we noticed,
we can do some of it together.
我们看到，当我们删除点x时，它比删除点y慢得多。
We saw that when we deleted point x,
it was way slower than deleting point y.
三角测量有点困难，
It was kinda hard to triangulate whyy,
因为为什么其中一个比另一个慢，对吗？
cuz why is one of these
slower than the other, right?
但是当我们和三个人一起做的时候，我们可以想出一个办法，
But when we do it with three,
we can kinda like figure out,
其中一个和另一个不一样，而且
one of this is not like the other, and
找出这三个人中哪个是怪人。
figure out which of
the three is the oddball.
是删除x，第一个，
Is deleting x, the first one,
古怪的人，还是正在删除y，第二个，古怪的人？
the oddball, or is deleting y,
the second one, the oddball?
但我们不知道，但当我们有三个的时候，你就能知道谁错了。
But we don't know, but when we have three,
you can figure out who's wrong.
所以让我们继续，让我们尝试一下，让我继续。
So let's go ahead,
let's try it out, let me go ahead.
我有Point(2，4，6)，我有我的构造函数。
I have Point (2, 4, 6),
I've got my constructor.
让我继续保存并运行它。
Let me go ahead and save it and run it.
&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：好吧，所以删除x肯定还是很慢的，
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: All right, so
deleting x was definitely still slow,
这一点没有改变。
that hasn't changed.
&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：删除y以前很快，现在很慢。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Deleting y was
fast before, it's now slow.
&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：删除z，&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：is，
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Deleting z,
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Is,
再来一次，对吗？
again, fast again,right?
所以以前，当我们只有x和y，&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：x很慢，
So before, when we only had x and y,
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: x was slow,
Y和其他一切都差不多。
y was about the same as everything else.
当我们加上z时，z是快的，其他两个是慢的。
When we added z, z was fast and
the other two were slow.
我们准备好做出假设了吗？
Are we ready to make a hypothesis yet?
就是这样，x很慢，或者
Which is it, that x was slow, or
当我们第一次看到它的时候y是可疑的快，现在z是？
that y was suspiciously fast when we
first looked at it, and now z is?
对，在我看来，如果我们删除最后一个，我们就没事了。
Right, seems to me that if we
delete the last one, we're okay.
如果我们删除第一个或第二个，
If we delete any of the first or
second ones,
我们突然变得慢了很多，这公平吗？
we all of sudden have gotten a lot slower,
is that fair?
对，有趣，对，这不应该真的很重要。
Right, interesting, right,
it shouldn't really matter.
它实际上，只是有趣的历史事实，它曾经是，从来不删除任何东西，因为
It actually, just fun historical fact, it
used to be, never delete anything because
删除任何属性都会减慢对象的速度。
deleting any of the properties
would have slowed the object down.
对，这是真的，在涡扇之前，有曲轴，而且
Right, and that was true, before Turbofan,
there was Crankshaft, and
如果删除任何属性，曲轴将变慢。
Crankshaft would get slower if you
deleted any of the properties.
涡扇稍微聪明一点，知道你是否删除了最后一个，
Turbofan is slightly smart enough
to know if you delete the last one,
很多时候就是你要删除的那个，它针对这种情况进行了优化。
which a lot of times is the one you're
deleting, it's optimized for that case.
但是删除属性很慢，这就像，谁在乎呢？
But deleting properties is slow,
which is like, who cares?
JavaScript是一种动态语言，对吧，它不应该真的很重要。
JavaScript's a dynamic language,
right, it shouldn't really matter.
我们有一定的洞察力来了解字符串和
We have some amount of insight
to know that strings and
数字绝对起了作用。
numbers definitely made a difference.
我们看到Turbofan能够标记一些优化的东西，并且
We saw Turbofan be able to mark
something for optimization, and
然后必须去优化它，对吗？
then have to deoptimize it, right?
所以几乎就像有一个类型系统在适当的地方。
So it's almost like there's
a type system in place.
我没有看到一个类型系统，对吧，我没有写流程或原因ML或打字稿。
I don't see a type system, right, I'm not
writing flow or reason ML or typescript.
但我确实感受到了一些影响。
But I'm definitely feeling
some of the effects of this.
而是一个可以具有所有这些不同属性的对象
But an object that could have all
these different properties on
它不同于字符串或数字。
it is different than something
that's a string or a number.
对，所以我从一些科学研究中感觉到了这一点，
Right, so I'm sensing this from
doing some of the science,
但我还不完全知道发生了什么。
but I don't totally know
what's happening yet.
让我做另一个小实验，我们将拿一堆物体。
Let me do another little experiment, and
we're gonna take a bunch of objects.
我们会稍微回到加法，
We're gonna go back to
addition a little bit,
因为谁不喜欢一些老式的加法？
cuz who doesn't like some
good old fashioned addition?
我们会继续，我们会拿一堆东西。
We'll go ahead,
we'll take a bunch of objects.
我们说的是常量对象，我只是要做一堆相同的对象。
We'll say const objects, and I'm just
gonna make a bunch of the same objects.
我会说a是1，a是2，
I'll say a is 1, a is 2,
A是3，A是4，所以这些非常
a is 3, a is 4, so these are very
相似的物体。
similar looking objects.
对，他们都有一个属性，一个属性总是一个数字。
Right, they all have an a property,
that a property is always a number.
对，希望你能做出一些假设
Right, hopefully you're making some
assumptions about what's gonna
发生在这里。
happen here.
对，就像，相似的东西好，不同的东西不好。
Right, it's like, similar things good,
different things bad.
对，所以拿着这个
Right, so take that and
我们继续说，设sum=0。
we'll go ahead and say, let sum = 0.
我们会得到一个物体。
We'll get one of the objects.
&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：这将有效地，迭代通过它。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: This will effectively
just, iterations move through it.
它将有效地结束为0，1，2，3，这将是索引。
It'll effectively end up being 0,
1, 2, 3, which'll be the indices.
所以我们要用这个旋转物体。
So we're just gonna rotate
through the objects with this.
&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：我们会说总和等于总和
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: And
we'll say sum equals sum
加上，&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：a property
plus,
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: The a property
那个物体的。
of that object.
对，所以要经过多少次，对吧，
Right, so go through, for
however many times, right,
我们要检查这些物体。
we're gonna go through the objects.
我们要添加a属性，我们要添加a属性，
We're gonna add the a property,
we're gonna add the a property,
我们要一遍又一遍地添加a属性。
over and over and over again.
让我们看看我们得到了什么。
Let's see what we get.
&gt；&gt；steve kinney：好的，大约花了9毫秒，
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: All right,
took about nine milliseconds,
我相信我们可以回到1E7。
I feel confident we can go back up to 1E7.
&gt；&gt；steve kinney：好的，26，对，
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: All right, 26, right,
显然这里的伸缩性很好，好的，还不错。
clearly scaling pretty well here,
okay, not bad.
我们继续吧，我们要保留他们所有人的财产，
Let's go ahead, we're gonna keep
an a property on all of them,
因为这个代码理论上会，我甚至不知道如果我们输了会发生什么。
cuz this code would theoretically,
I don't even know what happens if we lose.
我猜未定义者被强迫进入NaN，没有人愿意走这条路。
I guess undefined gets coerced into NAN,
nobody wants to go down that road.
所以我们会保留他们所有人的财产。
So we'll keep an a property
on all of them.
但也许有时候我们在一个物体上添加了一些东西，
But maybe sometimes we added
some stuff to an object,
有时我们从对象中删除一些内容，事情发生在JavaScript中。
sometimes we deleted some stuff from
an object, things happen in JavaScript.
对，我们的代码是一个狂野的地方，事情一直在变化。
Right, our code's a wild, wild place,
things are changing all the time.
我们从数据库中得到了不同的数据，而且
We've got back different
data from the database, and
他们中的一些人有这些属性，有些人没有。
some of them have these properties,
some of them don't.
所以我们会继续说，给这个a，b属性。
So we'll go ahead and say,
give this one a b property.
&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：在这里我们说，&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：让我们
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Here we'll say,
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Let's
让他们与众不同。
make them different.
&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：好的，我们将再次运行此代码。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: All right,
we'll run this code again.
&gt；&gt；steve kinney：好的，又是几毫秒，但是
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: All right, that's,
again, a few milliseconds, but
这绝对是一个明显的差异，那是20%的长，对吗？
that's definitely a noticeable difference,
that's 20% longer, right?